<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Politically Math</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Politically Math</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.139.3</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The State and The Pandemic Models in India</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/the-state-and-the-pandemic-models-in-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/the-state-and-the-pandemic-models-in-india/</guid>
      <description>India reached a milestone on October 22, 2021 of managing a health crisis, Covid-19, by administering [1 billion](https://web.archive.org/web/20220403072424/https://www.hindustantimes.com/india-news/the-numbers-behind-india-s-billion-dose-landmark-101634831247898.html) covax dosages to its population. Although the situation was completely different when the Supreme Court of India in a [suo-moto case](https://web.archive.org/web/20220403072424/https://www.livelaw.in/top-stories/supreme-court-centres-vaccine-policy-prima-facie-detrimental-to-right-to-health-article-14-21-173474) inquired the Central government on vaccine procurements, the dual prices of Vaccines, and its accessibility when the country was reeling under the fatal second wave earlier this year. The progress of vaccination, however, now seems to be on track, and a silver line amid the chaotic times from the start of the Pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manifesto</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/manifesto/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/manifesto/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;manifesto&#34;&gt;Manifesto&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;excerpt&#34;&gt;Excerpt&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Section 1&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Who would deny logic? Every simple person uses logic without the guidance of a logician, but logic that attempts to prove the soul, the god, or the supernatural cannot be considered valid. The common person would believe any of this without some obscurantist logician creating confusion.” - - Carvaka&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In every age the old gods fall to new. Today the gods are data and programs. They see us. They govern our fate, and they will guide us to our destiny.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
